question_data = [
{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Entertainment: Film","question":"'Minions' was released on the June 10th, 2015.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Entertainment: Video Games","question":"Rollercoaster Tycoon 1 and 2 were developed by Chris Sawyer.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Entertainment: Video Games","question":"'Sonic the Hedgehog 2' originally was going to have a time travel system.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga","question":"In Chobits, Hideki found Chii in his apartment.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Entertainment: Video Games","question":"Super Mario Bros. was the first video game ever created.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Entertainment: Film","question":"Samuel L. Jackson had the words, 'Bad Motherf*cker' in-scripted on his lightsaber during the filming of Star Wars.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"General Knowledge","question":"The Sun rises from the North.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga","question":"In the 1988 film 'Akira', Tetsuo ends up destroying Tokyo.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Entertainment: Music","question":"John Williams composed the music for 'Star Wars'.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Entertainment: Video Games","question":"In the Super Mario series, the character Pauline is a Princess like Princess Peach.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]}
]
